<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.jpg" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Dolphin
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/cms/Dolphin
	</ratings>
	<space>
		63820603
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.boonex.com/dolphin/
	</support>
	<version>
		7.4.2
	</version>
	<mod>38</mod>
	<release_date>18-04-2019</release_date>
	<admin>administration</admin>
	<min_require>7.4.1</min_require>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.4.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="curl" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="mbstring" /> 
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="gd" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="json" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="zip" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="openssl" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="xsl" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Dolphin</font> is the world's most advanced community software. Open-source, independent, downloadable, scalable, customizable, full-featured, free software for building social networks, dating sites and web-communities.
		<br /><br />
Loaded with video chat, recorder, video player, forums, groups, events, video messenger, mailbox, desktop app, video sharing, photo sharing, iPhone app and much more. Build your own business or advance your hobby with Dolphin! 
		<br /><br />
		Dolphin is free software. This work is licensed under a <a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/" target="_blank">Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 License</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
		<h1>Create your own kick-ass community site!</h1>
		<p class="b9-p-first">
	YouTube, MySpace, Odeo, Flickr, Match and Facebook - all in one, customizable and under 
	your full control. You're limited only by your imagination - not by software. Dolphin Smart 
	Community Builder is a universal, free, open source software that allows you to build any kind 
	of online community. With a huge variety of features &amp; options, you can quickly launch your 
	very unique and successful website.    
		</p>                

		<h2>Online dating software, social networking software and an advanced CMS - all in one, all finely tuned.</h2>

		<p>
	Create dating sites, social networks, video  sharing portals - you name it. Dolphin includes all 
	the features of dating scripts and adds more. You just build the site of your dreams and 
	deploy it instantly with the ease and elegance that only Dolphin can provide. For Free.    
		</p>
		
		<h2>Open source. Open community. Open borders.</h2>
		<p>
	Dolphin provides simple yet sophisticated tools to build your own community site, but you can 
	go further with the power of open source and a large, helpful and active community with over 
	50,000 members - BoonEx Unity.
		</p>

		<h2>Forums, Photos, Video, Music, Blogs, Polls, Events, Groups, Chat, Messenger, Boards, Design Templates and Languages!</h2>

		<p>
	When it comes to features, nothing comes close to Dolphin. Moreover, with our renowned 
	“Builders” and powerful admin tools you can mix’n’twist site features, navigation, design and 
	text to make it truly unique. You can go further by adding Extensions from 3rd party providers
	available at BoonEx Unity.
		</p>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>