<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/WebCalendar
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/calendars/WebCalendar
	</ratings>
	<space>
		5605833
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.k5n.us/webcalendar.php
	</support>
	<version>
		1.3.0
	</version>
	<mod>14</mod>
	<release_date>16-03-2019</release_date>
	<admin>admin.php</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="7.0.0" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">WebCalendar</font> is a PHP-based calendar application that can be configured as a single-user calendar, a multi-user calendar for groups of users, or as an event calendar viewable by visitors.<br /><br />

WebCalendar can be setup in a variety of ways, such as...<br />

    * A schedule management system for a single person<br />
    * A schedule management system for a group of people, allowing one or more assistants to manage the calendar of another user<br />
    * An events schedule that anyone can view, allowing visitors to submit new events<br />
    * A calendar server that can be viewed with iCalendar-compliant calendar applications like Mozilla Sunbird, Apple iCal or GNOME Evolution or RSS-enabled applications like Firefox, Thunderbird, RSSOwl, FeedDemon, or BlogExpress.<br />
		<br /><br />
		Web Calendar is released under the <a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html">GNU/GPL</a> terms.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
		<ul>
<li>XHTML/CSS compliance </li>
<li>Multi-user support </li>
<li>30 supported languages:
Basque,
Bulgarian,
Chinese-Big5,
Chinese-GB2312,
Czech,
Danish,
Dutch,
English-US,
Estonian,
Finnish,
French,
Galician,
German,
Greek,
Holo-Big5,
Hungarian,
Icelandic,
Italian,
Japanese,
Korean,
Norwegian,
Polish,
Portuguese_BR,
Portuguese,
Romanian,
Russian,
Spanish,
Swedish,
Turkish,
Welsh </li>

<li>Auto-detect user's language preference from browser settings </li>
<li>View calendars by day, week, month or year </li>
<li>View another user's calendar </li>
<li>View one or more users' calendar via layers on top of your own calendar </li>

<li>Add/Edit/Delete users </li>
<li>Add/Edit/Delete events </li>
<li>Repeating events including support for overriding or deleting (exceptions) </li>
<li>Configurable custom event fields </li>
<li>User-configurable preferences for colors, 12/24 time format, Sun/Mon week start </li>
<li>Online help </li>
<li>Checks for scheduling conflicts </li>
<li>Email reminders for upcoming events </li>
<li>Email notifications for new/updated/deleted events </li>

<li>Export events to iCalendar, vCalendar or Palm </li>
<li>Import from iCalendar, vCalendar or Palm </li>
<li>Optional general access (no login required) to allow
  calendar to be viewed by people without a login (useful
  for event calendars) </li>
<li>Users can make their calendar available publicly to anyone
  with an iCalendar-compliant calendar program (such as
  Apple's iCal, Mozilla Calendar or Sunbird)
  </li>
<li>Publishing of free/busy schedules (part of the iCalendar standard)
   </li>
<li>RSS support that puts a user's calendar into RSS
    (WebCalendar 1.1+)
</li><li>Subscribe to "remote" calendars (hosted elsewhere on the net)
    in either iCalendar or hCalendar formats
    (WebCalendar 1.1+)
    </li>
<li>User authentication: Web-based, HTTP, LDAP or NIS </li>

</ul>
		</english-features>		
	</languages>
</soft>