<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="oscommerce.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/osCommerce
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/ecommerce/osCommerce
	</ratings>
	<space>
		6947961
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.oscommerce.com
	</support>
	<version>
		2.3.4.1
	</version>
	<mod>17</mod>
	<mod_files>2</mod_files>
	<release_date>18-08-2017</release_date>
	<admin>admin</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.3.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="mcrypt" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">osCommerce</font> is an online shop e-commerce solution that offers a wide range of out-of-the-box features that allows online stores to be setup fairly quickly with ease, and is available for free as an Open Source based solution.
		<br /><br />
		osCommerce is released under the <a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/gpl-2.0.html" target="_blank">GNU/GPL license</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<ul>
<li>Compatible with PHP 4 and MySQL, easily portable to version 5.</li>
<li>Compatible with all major browsers.</li>
<li>Multi-lingual English, German and Spanish by default.</li>
<li>Automatic web-based installation.</li>
<li>Unlimited number of products and categories.</li>

<li>Automatic setup of e-commerce payment systems: Authorize.net, 2Checkout.com, iPayment.de, PayPal.com, PsiGate.com, SECPay.com, and TrustCommerce.com; Many other add-on ecommerce payment systems, off-line (manual) credit card payments) and on-line payment processing.</li>
<li>Multi-currency support via manual update from exchange rate server.</li>
<li>Support for dynamic images (one image per product).</li>
<li>Supports physical products as well as product downloads.</li>
<li>Web-based administration module.</li>

<li>Database backup and restore.</li>
<li>Temporary and permanent shopping carts.</li>
<li>Secure transactions with SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) support.</li>
<li>Many shipping options including by weight, price, or destination.</li>
<li>Real-time shipping quote integration with UPS, USPS.</li>
<li>Zone-based shipping options as well as a free shipping option as part of Order Totals Module.</li>
<li>Full tax functionality, included compounded taxes, different zones for different products.</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>