<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.png" style="float:right;margin:10px" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Coppermine
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/galleries/Coppermine
	</ratings>
	<space>
		7841092
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.coppermine-gallery.net/
	</support>
	<version>
		1.6.07
	</version>
	<mod>32</mod>
	<release_date>13-10-2019</release_date>
	<admin>login.php?referer=admin.php</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Coppermine</font> is a multi-purpose fully-featured and integrated web picture gallery script written in PHP using GD or ImageMagick as image library with a MySQL backend. <br /><br />
		CPG is so fully featured it's not enough to fully list them.
		Please click the Features Tab to see some of the features.
		<br /><br />
		Coppermine Photo Gallery (CPG) is an open source project released under the <a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html" target="_blank">GNU/GPL</a> terms.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
		<ul>
		   <li>arrangement of pictures in categories and albums;</li>
		   <li>picture information stored in database;</li>
		   <li>users can upload pictures with web interface or ftp (and admin can batch-add to database);</li>
		   <li>full multimedia support</li>
		   <li>creation of thumbnails and intermediate size pics;</li>
	
		   <li>search feature;</li>
		   <li>last added;</li>
		   <li>random picture;</li>
		   <li>user management (private galleries, groups);</li>
		   <li>integration of user management with various bbs (like phpBB, YaBB SE, SMF, Invisionboard, vbulletin);</li>
		   <li>caption, title, description and user defined fields for each picture (searchable);</li>
	
		   <li>easy install (installer provided);</li>
		   <li>multi-lingual: Arabian, Brazilian Portuguese, Bulgarian, Catalan, Chinese (both Big-5 and GB), Croatian, Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Estonian, Finnish, French, German (both "Du" and "Sie"), Greek, Hebrew, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Latvian, Malay, Norwegian, Polish, Romanian (both with and without diacritics), Russian, Slovenian, Spanish, Swedish, Uighur, Vietnamese; if your language is not on the list, you can easily create a translation for your own language;</li>
		   <li>user comments;</li>
		   <li>e-card feature;</li>
		   <li>slideshow viewer;</li>
		   <li>all features customizable with web interface (admin section);</li>
	
		   <li>template system;</li>
		   <li>user membership in multiple groups;</li>
		   <li>upload approval notice for admin;</li>
		   <li>EXIF/IPTC support;</li>
		   <li>language selection option in template;</li>
		   <li>image rotation;</li>
	
		   <li>multi-pic upload;</li>
		   <li>separation of the breadcrumb block so that it can be placed independently of category in the template;</li>
		   <li>option to choose max height or width for thumbnails will help in creating nicer looking thumbnail rows and cols;</li>
		   <li>option to display a clickable filmstrip of thumbnails below the image display;</li>
		   <li>option to show first level albums of a category instead of just statistics of the category;</li>
		   <li>option of turning on OR off the showing of "Private" Icon to unlogged / unprivileged user;</li>
	
		   <li>title option to sort in albums;</li>
		   <li>online help feature for the admin pages;</li>
		   <li>plugin-API;</li>
		   <li>English as a fallback language for un-translated entries in language files;</li>
		   <li>password-protected albums;</li>
		   <li>more admin-settable user profile fields;</li>
	
		   <li>picture-resize on upload;</li>
		   <li>bbs integration settable with a wizard-like user interface;</li>
		   <li>advanced search (boolean operators);</li>
		</ul>
		</english-features>
		<english-exp_ad_pass>New password. Leave blank if you do not want to reset the password</english-exp_ad_pass>
		<english-err_no_username>Please provide the username to reset the password</english-err_no_username>
		<english-err_no_such_user>The Admin username is incorrect and does not exist!</english-err_no_such_user>		
	</languages>
</soft>