<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right; margin:10px" width="250" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Vision_Helpdesk
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/customersupport/Vision_Helpdesk
	</ratings>
	<space>
		62345002
	</space>
	<support>
		http://support.visionhelpdesk.com/
	</support>
	<version>
		5.5.2
	</version>
	<mod>43</mod>
	<release_date>08-08-2019</release_date>
	<admin>manage/</admin>
	<min_require>4.0.0</min_require>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="7.1.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="curl" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="ionCube Loader" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Vision Helpdesk</font> offers customer service solutions for every size business, It offers three customer support solutions
		<br /><br /><b>1. Help Desk Software :</b> Multi channel customer support ticketing help desk that allows you to manage various channels like E-MAIL, WEB-FORMS, TWITTER, FACEBOOK, CHATS, CALLS everything under single roof.
		<br /><br /><b>2. Satellite / Multi Company Help Desk :</b> Manage your multiple brands or different companies customer support at centralized place, Setup different customer portal for each brand. Manage staff in different timezones and offer global customer support. 
		<br /><br /><b>3. IT Service Desk :</b> Service Desk software is enterprise level IT Help Desk that includes features from Help Desk and Satellite Help Desk additionally it offers ITIL / ITSM Modules - Incident, Problem, Change, Release, Contract, Financial Management, Service and Product Catalog, Vendor Management and more..
		<br /><br />
		You will need a Valid License key to install and run Vision Helpdesk.
		<br /><br />
		Vision Helpdesk is licensed under their <a href="https://www.visionhelpdesk.com/terms-and-conditions" target="_blank">Software License Agreement</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Online Issue Tracker</b></font><br />
Track issues online, Ticket creation using web interface and Email Parsing. Fetch emails using email piping, POP3, IMAP, POP3 SSL, IMAP SSL. Advance features like Two Way Email Parsing | Catch All Rules | Pre and Post Email parsing | manage Break-Lines<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Ticket Billing</b></font><br />
Prepaid and Postpaid Billing | Manage Credit | Create Invoice | Taxation | Bill Tickets Per Minute | Per Hour| Per Ticket | Per Post, Track Bill Time, Multi-Currency | Automation and much more..<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Blabby - Staff Collaboration </b></font><br />
Private Social Hub for your staff members to communicate, share knowledge | files | presentations | collaborate on ticket issues.<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Task Management</b></font><br />
simplified way to create, track and assign project tasks to multiple staff agents and link them to incidents.<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Help Desk Gamification</b></font><br />
Gamify your help desk platform by setting up agent achievement levels and quests<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Knowledge-base Management</b></font><br />
Predefined Replies for Staff, Manage Knowledgebase for Clients and Staff, Create Forums, Question and Answer, Bug Submission, Feature Requests, Manage Downloads and more..<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#6F8128"><b>Help Desk Automation</b></font><br />
Work Flow | SLA and Escalations — Automate your tickets work using rule based criteria and decide what action system should take on matching specific criteria conditions. Setup SLA's and offer timely response to tickets.
		</english-features>
		<english-exp_license>You can get free trial license <a href="http://www.visionhelpdesk.com/free-trial" target="_blank">here.</a></english-exp_license>
	</languages>
</soft>