<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Seo_Panel
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/others/Seo_Panel
	</ratings>
	<space>
		29890057
	</space>
	<support>
		https://www.seopanel.in/
	</support>
	<version>
		4.2.1
	</version>
	<mod>31</mod>
	<release_date>16-12-2019</release_date>
	<admin>login.php</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.4.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="curl" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="gd" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Seo Panel</font> A complete open source seo control panel for managing search engine optimization of your websites.<br /><br />
		Seo Panel is a seo tool kit includes latest hot seo tools to increase and track the performace of your websites.
		<br /><br />Any one can easily develop and install required plugins for their seo panel. 
		<br /><br />
		Seo Panel is released under <a href="http://www.seopanel.in/install/license/" target="_blank">GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE V2</a>.
		</english-overview>			
		<english-features>
		<ul>
				<li><strong>Automatic Directory Submission Tool</strong> : <br /> Automatic directory submission tool help us to submit our websites into to major free and paid internet directories. We can also track the status of each submision through periodical check using submission status checker script. Directory manager will help us to find out whether directory is active or not.</li>
				<li><strong>Keyword Position Checker</strong> :<br /> Keyword position checker will find the search engine position of targetted keywords of your website and stores it in the system. In keyword position reports section, we can see the daily positions of keywords in different search engines by beautiful graphs and detailed reports.</li>
				<li><strong>Site Auditor</strong> :<br /> Site Auditor will audit all SEO factors of each pages of a site and will give a detailed report about each page. This will help us to create XML,HTML,TEXT sitemap files of our website for submit to search engines.</li>

				<li><strong>Google and Alexa Rank Checker</strong> : <br />Google and alexa rank checker will find google pagerank and alexa rank of our websites and stores it in the system. In rank reports section, we can see the daily google and alexa rank of each website by detailed reports. </li>
				<li><strong>Backlinks Checker</strong> :<br /> Backlinks checker will find number of backlinks of our websites in different search engines(google,yahoo,msn etc) and stores it in the system.
In backlink reports section, we can see the daily backlinks count of each website by detailed reports. </li>
				<li><strong>Search Engine Saturation Checker</strong> : <br />Search Engine Saturation checker will find number of indexed pages of our websites in different search engines(google,yahoo,msn etc) and stores it in the system. In search engine saturation checker reports section, we can see the daily indexed page count of each website by detailed reports. </li>

				<li><strong>Multi Language Support</strong> :<br /> Seo panel can be used in multi languages and user can set their native language for thier session. Currently seo panel support 17 languages English, French, German, Polish, Italian, Romanian, Russian, Spanish, Dutch, Portuguese, Bulgarian, Hungarian, Chinese(traditional and simplified), Greek, Persian and Turkish .</li>
				<li><strong>Print and Export Reports</strong> : <br />You can easily print and export reports from seo panel and save it for future use. </li>
			</ul>
		</english-features>
		<english-company_name>Company Name</english-company_name>
	</languages>
</soft>