<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Open_Real_Estate
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/cms/Open_Real_Estate
	</ratings>
	<space>
		79717538
	</space>
	<support>
		http://open-real-estate.info/en/faq
	</support>
	<version>
		1.30.3
	</version>
	<mod>72</mod>
	<release_date>08-11-2019</release_date>
	<admin>site/login</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="7.0.0" />
	<requirement check="mysql" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.7.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="gd" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="curl" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="ctype" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="PDO" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="mbstring" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="pdo_mysql" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Open Real Estate</font> lets you create your own website to get the profits within the shortest possible time or to present your real estate agency on the Internet. An easy-to-use interface, high website speed, social tools, a variety of functions and add-ons – all this and some more help to build a business based on our products efficiently.
		<br /><br />
		Open Real Estate offers real estate agencies and real estate agents the technology they need to connect with real estate owners, prospective buyers and Internet surfers.
		<br /><br />
		Open Real Estate is released under the open source <a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/gpl-2.0.html" target="_blank">GNU GPL version 2</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
		<ul>
			<li>it is possible to post listings of property for sale and for rent with images, descriptions, displaying on the map;</li>
			<li>user is able to reserve a property online;</li>
			<li>user is able to send a message for booking a property with criteria he/she needs and his/her comments, the administrator is able to find and advise him/her an appropriate real estate;</li>
			<li>search through listings, sort by price and rate;</li>
			<li>all listings are displayed on the map;</li>
			<li>users can post comments and rate the listings;</li>
			<li>comments and rates can be displayed on the site at once or only after moderation by the administrator;</li>
			<li>each listing can have an image gallery (unlimited number of images);</li>
			<li>user can set a bookmark with publishing in social networks;</li>
			<li>the section News;</li>
			<li>the section Q&amp;As;</li>
			<li>management of site pages, ability to embed widgets (functional blocks) into pages;</li>
			<li>the listing can be marked as Special offer, and such a listing will be highlighted in search results;</li>
			<li>management of site parameters: cache settings, maps settings, settings of listings' displaying, settings of notifications for the administrator and users and many other parameters;</li>
		</ul>
		</english-features>
		<english-err_dbpass_len30>Database password cannot be more than 30 characters</english-err_dbpass_len30>
	</languages>
</soft>